Week 5. Day 1. False Friends. Egypt. Spanish. Actual. Currently. Rather than.
Especially. Bra. Swedish. Imagine. Sweden. Demand. Italian. Request. Command. Forceful.
Spill. Day 2. Heikikomori. Heikikomori. Withdraw. Confined. Go to great lengths.
Pull out. Phobia. Agoraphobia. Widespread. Bully. Snap. Confrontation. Attend to. Pursue.
Fend for oneself. Day 3. Wild Tasmania. Wombat. Devil. Miniature. Upside down. Bass straight.
Marsupial. Pouch. Growl. Mean. Appropriate. Burrow. Wallaby. Lay. Flora. Temperate. Eucalyptus.
Day 4. The Pygmalion Effect. Effect. Expect. Tend to. Expectation. Bother. Attach to. Demonstrate.
Randomly. Overall. Downside. Rise. Knock. Conduct. Versus. Praise. Inferior. Reverse. Day 5.
Say hello to our new mechanical friends. Mechanical. Lifestyle. Manufacturing. Industrial.
Assemble. Capable. Input. Laundry. Achieve. Affordable. Target. Sensitive. Delicate. Handy.
Livelihood. Day 6. Reusing versus recycling. Recycle. Throughout. Alternative. Object.
Original. Lengthen. Upgrade. Rag. In addition to. Breakdown. Pollute. Wasteful.